Arcadio Díaz Quiñones Papers, circa 1944-2019 (bulk 1970-2012 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 2: Correspondence, 1959-2019; 17 boxes (1 partial) 2 items
  - AM 2004-177, 1965-1983; 2 boxes
    - Davis, Natalie, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - de la Fuente, Alejandro, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Delgado, Sergio, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Di Tella, Andrés (Argentina), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Djurić, Djušan, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Droz, Vanessa, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Duchesne-Winter, Juan (Puerto Rico), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Ediciones Callejón (Puerto Rico), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Ellrich, Robert, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Estrada Vega, Ramón (Puerto Rico), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Estrade, Paul, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Fernández, James, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Fernández Bravo, Álvaro, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Fernández-Sein, Ani (Puerto Rico), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Ferré, Rosario, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Figueroa, Javier, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Firbas, Paul, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Florestal, Jean-Marie, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Fornet, Ambrosio (Cuba), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Fornet, Jorge (Cuba), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Fowler, Víctor (Cuba), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Fradera, Josep, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Fromm, Georg (Puerto Rico), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Fuentes, Francisco, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Funes, Fernando, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Funes, Reinaldo (Cuba), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - García, Gervasio L., dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - García Carranza, Araceli (Cuba), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - García Jaldón, Rafael (Madrid), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Garramuño, Florencia (Argentina), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Garrido, Ángel, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Gelpí, Juan, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Glantz, Margo, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - González, Beatriz, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - González, José Luis (Puerto Rico), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - González, Rodríguez, Sergio, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Gotay, Consuelo (Puerto Rico), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Gramuglio, María Teresa, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Grosfoguel, Ramón, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Guglieri, Araceli (Madrid), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Hantman, Daniel, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Hennessy, Alistair, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Hernández, Carmen Dolores, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Hernández, Orlando, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Hidalgo, Cecilia, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Hidalgo, Ibrahim (Cuba), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Hoetink, Harry, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Hoffman, François, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Holiday, David, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Homar, Lorenzo, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Hulme, Peter, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Ibarra, Jorge (Cuba), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Iglesia, Cristina (Argentina), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Iglesias, Alfonso (Cuba), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Iglesias, Marial (Cuba), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Jaksic, Ivan, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - King, Edmund, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Kramer, Paul, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Landreau, John C., dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Laws, George, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Leader, Alexandra, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Leggett, Gary, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Levy, Barbara, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Lewis, David (Puerto Rico), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Lleó, Conxita (Spain), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Llorens, Irma, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Lockwood, Bernard (Puerto Rico), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Long, Mary, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - López, Pedro Miguel (Spain), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - López, Sergio (Cuba), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - López-Adorno, Pedro, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Loureiro, Ángel, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Lugo-Ortiz, Agnes, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Luna, Noel (3 folders), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Manzi, Joaquín (Argentina, Francia), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Manzoni, Celina (Argentina), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Martínez, Juan José, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Martínez, Tomás Eloy (2 folders), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Martínez Shaw, Carlos, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Martorell, Antonio, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - McCook, Stuart (Princeton), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Melendes, Joserramón, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Meléndez, Héctor (Puerto Rico), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Millones, Luis (Perú), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Molloy, Sylvia, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Montero, Oscar, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Morales, Carlos Javier, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Morales, Haydée, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Morales, Jorge (2 folders), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Morales Z., Ana, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Morán, Francisco (Cuba, USA), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Morejón, Nancy, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Moreno Fraginals, Manuel R., dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Mota, Carlos Guilherme, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Múnera, Alfonso (Colombia), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Muñiz, Benjamin, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Navarra, Gilda, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Nistal, Benjamín, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - El Nuevo Día (Puerto Rico), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Nugent, Georgia, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Ochart Torres, Luz Ivonne, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Olea, Héctor, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Olea Franco, Rafael, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Orovio, Consuelo, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Pérez León, Roberto (Cuba), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Pérez Marín, Carmen I. (Puerto Rico), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Perivolaris, John, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Piglia, Ricardo, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Piñon, Nélida, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Pitol, Sergio, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Pizarro, Ana, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Premat, Julio, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Pruna, Pedro (Cuba), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Quijano, Aníbal (Perú), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Quijano, Nick, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Quiles, Edwin (Puerto Rico), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Quintero, Aramís (Cuba), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Quintero, Mareia (Puerto Rico), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Quintero Herencia, Juan Carlos, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Quintero Rivera, Ángel, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Rama, Ángel (2 folders), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Ramos Mattei, Antonio, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Redonet, Salvador (Cuba), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Reisz de Rivarola, Susana, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Rey, César, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Rigolot, François, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Rincón, Carlos, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Rivera, Marcia (Puerto Rico), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Rivera Pagán, Luis, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Rivera-Ramos, Efrén (Puerto Rico), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Rodríguez, Eugenio, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Rodríguez, María Elena (Puerto Rico), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Rodríguez, Pedro (Cuba), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Rodríguez, Pedro Pablo (Cuba), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Rodríguez, Reina María (Cuba), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Rodríguez Beruff, Jorge (Puerto Rico), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Rodríguez-Cepeda, Enrique (Madrid), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Rodríguez Garrido, José Antonio, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Rodríguez Puértolas, Julio, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Rojas, Rafael (Cuba), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Rosen, Virginia (New York), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Rotker, Susana, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Rudenstine, Neil L., dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Ruiz, Pablo, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Sábato, Hilda (Argentina), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Saer, Juan José, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Salgado, Cesar A. (Austin, Texas), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Samoilovich, Daniel, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Sánchez, Luis Rafael, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Sánchez Mejías, Rolando (Cuba), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Sánchez Robayna, Andrés, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Sandioca, Elena (Spain), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Sarlo, Beatriz, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Scarano, Mónica, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Schmitt, John, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Schwartz, Roberto, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Scott, Rebecca, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Segovia, Tomás, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Serrano Geyls, Raúl, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Shapiro, Harold T., dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Sherwin, Martín, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Shipley, George, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Simmons, Ruth, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Sommer, Doris, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Sorensen, Diana, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Sosnowski, Saúl, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Sotomayor, Aurea María, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Stein, Stanley, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Suárez Galbán, Eugenio, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Subirats, Eduardo, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Tineo, Gabriela, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Torres-Saillant, Silvio, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Trigo, Enrique, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Trujillo, Carlos Alberto, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Uitti, Karl D., dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Valdés, Juan Gabriel (Chile), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Vargas Llosa, Álvaro, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Vargas Llosa, Mario, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Vázquez, Hugo (Cuba), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Velázquez, Rosa, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Venegas, Carlos (Cuba), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Ventura, Roberto (Brazil), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Vera León, Antonio, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Vientós Gastón, Nilita (2 folders), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Vitier, Cintio, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Weiss, Nancy, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Wood, Michael, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Zanetti, Oscar (Cuba), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Díaz Quiñones, Arcadio, 1968; 1 box (1 partial)
      - cartas, copias, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
      - Claridad, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
      - El almuerzo en la hierba, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
      - Madrid, Lapesa—, 1968; 1 box (partial)
      - Arcadio and Alma (Madrid), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Princeton University, 1971-1981; 1 box (partial)
    - Universidad de Puerto Rico, 1965-1983; 1 box (1 partial)
      - (Mayagüez), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
      - Estudios Hispánicos—, 1965-1975; 1 box (partial)
      - 1983, 1 box (partial)
    - University of Washington (Seattle), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - "La memoria rota" I, II, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Memorabilia (3 folders), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
  - AM 2005-100, 1965-2005; 2 boxes
    - Alianza Editorial (Madrid), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Ateneo de Madrid, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Barrera López, Trinidad, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Bhabha, Homi K., dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Biblioteca Ayacucho (Caracas), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Britt, Christopher, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Buscaglia, José, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Carrión, Juan Manuel, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Cátedra (Madrid), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Chejfec, Sergio, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - City University of New York, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - CLACSO (Buenos Aires), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Cornejo Polar, Antonio, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Ediciones Santillana, Inc. (San Juan), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Editorial Plaza Mayor, Inc. (Puerto Rico), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Fernandez, Harold, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Fernandez Bravo, Alvaro, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Fuentes, Francisco, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - García, Gervasio, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - García Padilla, Antonio, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Garramuño, Florencia, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Girgus, Joan, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - González Calderón, María Elena, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - González de Mojica, Sarah, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - González, José Luis, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Hennessy, Alistair, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Hernández, Orlando, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Hirschman, Albert, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Hulme, Peter, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Iglesia, Cristina, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Instituto de Cultura Puertorriqueña, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Irby, James, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Johnson, Peter, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Josam, Hannelore, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Larrubia-Prado, Francisco, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Llorens, Irma, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Lockwood, Bernie, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - López, Pedro Miguel, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Lugo Ortiz, Agnes, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Macklin, Elizabeth, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Márquez, Roberto, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Martínez González del Campo, José M., dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Marzán, Julio, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Mekis Martinez, Federico, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Mellón, Juan Antón, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Millones, Luis, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Molinero, Rita, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Monsiváis, Carlos, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Montero, Oscar, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Noya, Elsa, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - POSTDATA (San Juan), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Premio Juan Rulfo (Guadalajara), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Princeton University, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Rodríguez, Pedro, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Rodríguez Luis, Julio, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Rosman, Silvia, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Rudenstine, Neil, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Rutgers University, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Scott, Rebecca, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Shipley, George, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Sin Nombre (San Juan), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Solá, María M., dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Sorensen, Diana, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Soto, Valentín, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Subirats, Eduardo, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Sullivan, Edward, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Tcherkaski, Osvaldo, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Trigo Tió, Enrique, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Universidad Autónoma de Santo Domingo, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Universitat Pompeu Fabra (Barcelona), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - University of North Carolina Press, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Ventura, Roberto, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Vientós Gastón, Nilita, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Vitier, Carlos, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Zanetti, Oscar, dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
    - Memorabilia (three folders), dates not examined; 1 box (partial)
  - AM 2007-4; AM 2016-95; AM 2017-33; AM 2017-99; 2019-114, 1959-2019; 7 boxes (1 partial)
    Material in Series 4, Box 19 is restricted until 2027.
    - Abreu, Adorno, circa 1990s-2000s; 1 box (partial)
    - Achúgar, Hugo, 1993; 1 box (partial)
    - Adelman, Jeremy, circa 1990s; 1 box (partial)
    - Adorno, Rolena, circa 1989-1995; 1 box (partial)
    - Aguilar, Gonzalo (Argentina), 1998; 1 box (partial)
    - Agnew, Deborah, 1987; 1 box (partial)
    - Alberty, Carlos, 1983; 1 box (partial)
    - Alicéa, José R. (Puerto Rico), 2019; 1 box (partial)
    - Allen, Jenny, circa 1989; 1 box (partial)
    - Allen, Marnie, 1973, 2006; 1 box (partial)
    - Allen, Stephen, 2004, 2016; 1 box (partial)
    - Altamirano, Carlos (Argentina), 1999, 2006; 1 box (partial)
    - Altamirano, Carlos; Díaz, Arcadio; Quilmes - Intelectuales, circa 2007; 1 box (partial)
    - Alvarez Curbelo, Silvia (Puerto Rico), 1990; 1 box (partial)
    - Alvarez, José, 1988; 1 box (partial)
    - Amherst College, 1988; 1 box (partial)
    - Amelang, Jim, 1986-1989; 1 box (partial)
    - Anderman, Jens, 1998; 1 box (partial)
    - Andreu Iglesias, César (Puerto Rico), 2019; undated; 1 box (partial)
    - Antelo, Raúl, 1998; 1 box (partial)
    - Antón Mellon, Juan, 1995; 1 box (partial)
    - Aponte, Barbara, circa 1977; 1 box (partial)
    - Archivo General de Indias, 1964; 1 box (partial)
    - Asociación de Estudios Dominicanos, 2007; 1 box (partial)
    - Asociación Puertorriqueña de Historiadores, 2011; 1 box (partial)
    - Asociación Puertorriqueña de Profesores Universitarios, circa 1971; 1 box (partial)
    - Archetti, Eduardo P., 1994; 1 box (partial)
    - Arnold, James, 1994; 1 box (partial)
    - Azize, Yamila, 1980; 1 box (partial)
    - Bacmeister, Citlali, undated; 1 box (partial)
    - Báez, Myrna, circa 2000-2002; 1 box (partial)
    - Baena del Alcázar, Fernando, circa 1964; 1 box (partial)
    - Balsa, Miguel, 2007; 1 box (partial)
    - Barash, Carol, 1991; 1 box (partial)
    - Barrera, Joel, circa 1986-1988; 1 box (partial)
    - Barrera, Trinidad (Sevilla), circa 1989-1995; 1 box (partial)
    - Bastos, María Luisa, 1987; 1 box (partial)
    - Bedoya, Rosario, 1998; 1 box (partial)
    - Behar, Ruth, circa 1990s-2013; 1 box (partial)
    - Beezley, William, 1991; 1 box (partial)
    - Bell, Lydia, 2009; 1 box (partial)
    - Ben Joussef, Nadia, 2006; 1 box (partial)
    - Benítez Rojo, Antonio, circa 1990s-2000s; 1 box (partial)
    - Berg, Edgardo H. (Argentina), 1993; 1 box (partial)
    - Bermann, Sandra, 1999; 1 box (partial)
    - Bernecker, Walther L., 1997; 1 box (partial)
    - Berry, Charles, 1988; 1 box (partial)
    - Betancourt, Virginia (Venezuela), circa 1973; 1 box (partial)
    - Bhabha, Homi, 1992; 1 box (partial)
    - Biblioteca Ayacucho, circa 1970s-1990s; 1 box (partial)
    - Binder, Wolfgang, circa 1997; 1 box (partial)
    - Blades, Rubén, circa 1997; 1 box (partial)
    - Blanco, Guillermo (Cuba), circa 1997; 1 box (partial)
    - Blanco, John, 2000-2001; 1 box (partial)
    - Blasco, Javier, 1991-1992; 1 box (partial)
    - Bonilla, Frank, 1986, 2011; 1 box (partial)
    - Bonilla, Frank y Nelida Pérez, undated; 1 box (partial)
    - Bowen, William, circa 1986-1988; 1 box (partial)
    - Brombert, Victor, circa 1982-1984; 1 box (partial)
    - Brune, Krista, 2006; 1 box (partial)
    - Bueno, Raúl, circa 1987-1990; 1 box (partial)
    - Bulletin of Latin American Research, 2004; 1 box (partial)
    - Buscaglia, José, circa 1990s-2017; 1 box (partial)
    - Buscaglia-Guillermety, José, circa 1988-1991; 1 box (partial)
    - Buscaglia-Salgado, José, 2006; 1 box (partial)
    - Bush, Andrew, 1989; 1 box (partial)
    - Bystrom, Kerry, 2005, 2010; 1 box (partial)
    - Cabán, Pedro, circa 1989-1992; 1 box (partial)
    - Cabrera, Anna, 2018; 1 box (partial)
    - Cairo, Ana (Cuba), circa 1990s-2018; 1 box (partial)
    - Campuzano, Luisa (Cuba), 1999; 1 box (partial)
    - Calvo, Hortensia, 1993; 1 box (partial)
    - Canino, María, 2001; 1 box (partial)
    - Cardenal, Ernesto (Nicaragua), 1980; 1 box (partial)
    - Caribbean Symposium, 1994; 1 box (partial)
    - Carbonell, Jorge, circa 1999-2004; 1 box (partial)
    - Carrasco, David, circa 1992; 1 box (partial)
    - Carrera, Arturo, undated; 1 box (partial)
    - Carrión, Juan Manuel, 1986-1992; 1 box (partial)
    - Carta abierta al secretario de educación, Puerto Rico, 1998; 1 box (partial)
    - Castañeda, Jorge, circa 1986-1990s; 1 box (partial)
    - Castillo Griñán, Raúl (Cuba), 1995; 1 box (partial)
    - Cedrón, Tata (Argentina), 1994; 1 box (partial)
    - Centro de Estudios Puertorriqueños (N.Y.), 2009, 2011; 1 box (partial)
    - Centro de Estudios Puertorriqueños (CUNY), 1983; 1 box (partial)
    - CEREP (Centro de Estudios de la Realidad Puertorriqueña), circa 1980s-2011; 1 box (partial)
    - CEREP (Puerto Rico), José Curet, 1979, 1985; 1 box (partial)
    - CEREP (Puerto Rico), Marcia Rivera, circa 1981-1990; 1 box (partial)
    - CEREP - Seminario verano, 1975; 1 box (partial)
    - Centro - Journal of the Center for Puerto Rican Studies, 2001; 1 box (partial)
    - Chang-Rodríguez, Raquel, 1991; 1 box (partial)
    - Chejfec, Sergio (Argentina - Venezuela), 1991; 1 box (partial)
    - Chow, Paula, 1982; 1 box (partial)
    - CLACSO (Chile), 1991; 1 box (partial)
    - CLACSO/Marcia Rivera (Consejo Latinoamericano de Ciencas Sociales), circa 1993; 1 box (partial)
    - Claridad (Puerto Rico), 1991; 1 box (partial)
    - Claudia, 2011; 1 box (partial)
    - Club de Amigos de la UNESCO (Madrid), 1986; 1 box (partial)
    - Coatsworth, John, 1989; 1 box (partial)
    - Cobo Borda, Juan Gustavo (Colombia), circa 1987; 1 box (partial)
    - Colegio de México - Coloquio - Pedro Henríquez Ureña, 2006; 1 box (partial)
    - Colegio de México - Coloquio - Saer y Piglia, 2005; 1 box (partial)
    - Colombi, Beatriz (Argentina), 1994; 1 box (partial)